Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - Eleo Pomare, Thurs. Feb. 4, Sat. Feb. 6, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Alvin Ailey, Mon., Jan. 18-Sat. Jan. 30, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Alwin Nikolais, Mon., Feb. 22-Sat., Mar. 6, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Dance Theatre Of Harlem, Mon. Mar. 8, Wed. Mat. Mar. 10, Fri. Mar. 12, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Erick Hawkins, Tues. Mar. 9, Wed. Mar. 10, Sat. Mat. Mar. 13, 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Don Redlich Dance Company, City Center, Thurs., Mar. 11, Sat., Mar. 13, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theatre, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Ailey, City Center II (Box 49)
  - Ad Copy, Press Releases, Publicity, Program Copy (Box 49)
  - Sets and Props (Box 49)
  - Contracts (Company Union, Etc.) (Box 49)
  - Preliminary Notes and Letters (Box 49)
  - Gerry Tarrack, Jenny Tipton (Box 49)
  - Norman Singer (Box 49)
  - City Center, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
  - City Center, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
  - City Center, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
  - City Center, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
  - City Center, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
  - City Center, 1969-1972 (Box 49)
  - Scott, Judith Laura, Foreign Canada Resident Students (B-3536), 1970 (Box 50)
  - Calendar for June, Letters to A.Councils, Re: Distribution (Box 50)
  - National Endowment Calendar (Box 50)
  - Evaluations CRTP., 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - SAC Grant Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program, 1972-1974 (Box 50)
  - CRTP General Cumulative Stats, Residency Count/Co., 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Alabama Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Alabama SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Alabama Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Alaska Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Arizona Sac Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Arizona Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Arizona Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Arkansas Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - California SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - California Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - California, CAC, Letters to Local Sponsors, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - California Cash Requests and Records, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - California Payment of NEA Funds (Memos, Contracts, Etc), 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - California CRTP, Contracts, Schedules, Invoices, Related Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - California NEA Funds, Contracts, Memos, Etc, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - California Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Colorado Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Colorado SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Colorado Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Connecticut SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Connecticut Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence, Letter, Susan Hunter and Sue Cohen, Alvin Ailey, Oct. 3, 1973 (Box 50)
  - California Dance Project, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 50)
  - Connecticut Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Delaware Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Delaware SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Delaware Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Florida Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Florida SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Florida Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Georgia Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Hawaii Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Hawaii Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Hawaii SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Illinois SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Illinois Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Illinois Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Indiana Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Indiana SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Indiana Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Iowa Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Iowa SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Iowa Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Kentucky Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Kentucky SAC Grant Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Kentucky Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Louisiana SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Louisiana Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Louisiana Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Maine Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Maine Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Maine SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Maine Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Maryland SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Maryland Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Maryland Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Massachusettes State Arts Council Grant, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Distribution of Massachusettes State Arts Council Money to Local Sponsors, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Massachusettes Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Massachusettes Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Michigan SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Michigan Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Michigan Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Minnesota SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Minnesota Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Minnesota Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Missouri SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Missouri Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Missouri Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Montana Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Montana Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Nebraska Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Nebraska Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
  - Portsmouth, NH (Portsmouth School Dept./Little Harbour) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Portsmouth, New Hampshire, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Grand Forks, ND (Ben Franklin School/Grand Forks School District #1) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Toledo, OH (Arts Commission Of Greater Toledo) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Toledo, Ohio, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Elizabethtown, PA (E-Town Area School District) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Elizabethtown, Pennsylvania, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Aberdeen, SD (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Aberdeen, South Dakota, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Pleasant Grove, UT (Pleasant Grove High School) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Pleasant Grove, Utah, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two Dance Component, Panel Memo and Decisions, 1978-1989 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two Panel Results, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - AIS/DC Phase Two Applications, Extra Copies, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two Schools' Requests for Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two Deadlines, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two Miscellaneous Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - AIS Phase Two Applicant Call Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Blank Forms (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, AMES, Iowa, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - Ames, IA (Ames Community Schools) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, South Burlington, Vermont, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
  - South Burlington, VT (SO. Burlington School District) (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Marshalltown, Iowa, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Waltham, Massachusettes, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Lake Placid, New York, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, High Point, North Carolina, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Devils Lake, North Dakota, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Salem, Oregon, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Tucson, Arizona, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Waipahu, Hawaii, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Pineville, Louisiana, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Gorham, Maine, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, East Brunswick, New Jersey, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, New York, New York, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Lima, Ohio, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Warren, Ohio, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Hempfield, Pennsylvania, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Saint Andrews, Tennessee, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Phase Two, Ogden, Utah, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Memo, Dec. 19, 1979 (Box 51)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Group Leaders and Expectations Speakers, 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Technique and Workshop Classes, 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Workshop, Expenses, Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Evaluations and Group Leader Reports, 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS, To Do, 1979-1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Workshop, Number of Observers, 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Kit Materials, 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Artists' Kit Materials (Special), 1980 (Box 51)
  - AIS Planning Meeting, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Printed Materials, Directory of Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1980-1981 (Box 51)
  - Printed Materials, FYI (Newsletter), June 1981 (Box 51)
  - Printed Materials, Sampler Information, 1981 (Box 51)
  - Printed Materials, Sampler Information, 1981 (Box 51)
  - AIS/Dance Component Workshop, July 29, 1972 (Box 52)
  - AIE Film Correspondence, 1981 (Box 52)
  - AIE Film Correspondence, 1980 (Box 52)
  - Film Requests, Forms, Logs, Etc (Box 52)
  - Grant No. A30-51-1 to City Center for AIS/DC Reg. Mtgs./Hdbk/Film, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - AIS Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - Dance Movement Teacher Contracts for AIS 1972-1973, but reimbursed in 1973-1974, 1973-1974 (Box 52)
  - AIS Mvt. Teacher Completed Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - AIS Dance Component Film, 1973-1974 (Box 52)
  - AIS Grant Letters, NEA:NYSC, Grant A 40-51-43 (Box 52)
  - AIS Ledger Sheets and Calendar, 1974-1975 (Box 52)
  - AIS Summer Accounting Final Accounting, 1974-1975 (Box 52)
  - AIS Grant A 40-51-43 Budget and Estimated Expenditures, 1974-1975 (Box 52)
  - Final Report, NYFA, Grant A40-51-43, 1974-1975 (Box 52)
  - Indiana, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Illinois, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Iowa, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Kansas (Box 52)
  - Louisiana, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Maine, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Maryland (Box 52)
  - Massachusetts, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Michigan, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Minnesota, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Missouri, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Nevada, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - New Hampshire, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - New Mexico, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - New Jersey, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - New York (Box 52)
  - New York, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - New York, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
  - Oregon, 1976-1977 (Box 53)
  - Pennsylvania, 1976-1977 (Box 53)
  - Puerto Rico, 1976-1977 (Box 53)
  - South Dakota, 1976-1977 (Box 53)
  - Sample AIS Kit, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Artists' Agenda, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Originals of Memos Sent, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Workshop, Planning for Next Year, Jazz Component, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Workshop, Chuck Davis Company Performance, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Workshop, Attendance Exceptions, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Memo to the States, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Speaker/Group Leader Suggestions from Artists, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, General Sessions, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS/Dance Component Workshop, Kit Materials not Used, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Agenda, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS/Jazz Component, Notes and General Information, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Welcome and Introduction, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Letters from Kids for Expectations, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS/Dance Component Workshop, Workshop Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Special Miscellaneous Invitations, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Attendance Exceptions for Workshop, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Independent Screenings/Presentations, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, VIP Housing and Hospitality, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Independent Screenings, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Job-Alikes, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Space/Equipment Requests to Anne, 1980 (Box 53)
  - Summer Workshop Independent Screenings, 1980 (Box 53)
  - Jazz Component (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Memos to Jean Danser/Lisa Booth, 1980 (Box 53)
  - Summer Workshop, Registration Procedure and Notes, 1980 (Box 53)
  - Summer Workshop Space, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Staff Assignments/Work Force, 1980 (Box 53)
  - Summer Workshop Work Force, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Kit Materials, 1980 (Box 53)
  - AIS Summer Workshop, Expenses, Travel Reimbursement (forms), 1980 (Box 53)
  - R70-51-95N AIS Handbook Grant Expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 53)
  - AIS Handbook Grant, R70-51-95N, Laura Shapiro Edition Application, 1977-1978 (Box 53)
  - AIS Handbook Grant #R70-51-95N, Cash Requests (Box 53)
  - Sampler Program Information Expenses, 1981-1982 (Box 53)
  - Dancing in the Schools (Box 53)
  - Current Workshop Projected Budget, 1981 (Box 53)
  - ADF Program Deposit Sheets, Summer Workshop, 1981 (Box 53)
  - AIS/Dance Component Grant 02-5150-072 Cash Requests, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - AIE Workshop Planning Meeting For Workshop, 1981 (Box 53)
  - Grant Surplus, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - Video Projects, Amy Greenfield (Box 53)
  - Final Grant Report, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - Final Grant Report, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - Arts In Education Grant Renewal Application, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - North Carolina, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - North Dakota, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - Ohio, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - Oklahoma, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program, Directory of Dance Companies, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program, Directory of Dance Companies, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program, Directory of Dance Companies, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program, Directory of Dance Companies, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines for Sponsors, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program Application Guidelines, 1980-1981 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program Application Guidelines, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program Application Guidelines, 1979-1980 (Box 54)
  - Artists In Schools Application Guidelines, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Artists In Schools Program Information, 1977-1978 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines For Sponsors, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines For State Arts Agencies, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Dance Touring Program, Directory of Dance Companies, Touring Season 1978-1979, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Company Forms, Complete, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 54)
  - Company Memorandum, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 1971 (Box 54)
  - State Arts Council Correspondence, 1971 (Box 54)
  - Co. Interim Status Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Company Lists, Twenty Seven Companies, Master Copies, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Problem, Solutions, CRTP, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Local Sponsor Memorandum, 1971 (Box 54)
  - Project Grant Applications, National Endowment For The Arts Coordinated Residency Touring Program, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Mid-Atlantic Circuit (Box 54)
  - New England Circuit (Box 54)
  - Northwest Circuit (Box 54)
  - West Circuit (Box 54)
  - Central Southwest Circuit (Box 54)
  - Midwest Circuit (Box 54)
  - South Circuit (Box 54)
  - Great Lakes Circuit (Box 54)
  - Local Sponsors Return Slips, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Local Sponsors Return Slips, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Foreign Touring Lists (Box 55)
  - Asia (Box 55)
  - Australia (Box 55)
  - Canada (Box 55)
  - England and Ireland (Box 55)
  - France (Box 55)
  - Holland and Belgium (Box 55)
  - Italy, Greece, Spain, Portugal (Box 55)
  - Germany, Switzerland, Austria (Box 55)
  - Iceland, Norway, Finland (Box 55)
  - Mexico (Box 55)
  - Sweden (Box 55)
  - South America (Box 55)
  - Near East, Turkey, Lebanon (Box 55)
  - Yugoslavia, Poland, Czechoslovakia, Romania (Box 55)
  - Alabama, Arizona, Florida, Georgia (Box 55)
  - Alaska, Washington, Idaho, Oregon, California (Box 55)
  - Colorado, Idaho, Kansas, Minnesota, Montana, Nebraska, Utah (Box 55)
  - Connecticut, Vermont, Massachusettes, New Hampshire, Rhode Island (Box 55)
  - Delaware, Maryland, North Carolina, South Carolina, Virginia (Box 55)
  - Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kentucky, Michigan, Ohio, Wisconsin (Box 55)
  - Louisiana, Mississippi, Missouri, New Mexico (Box 55)
  - New Jersey, Washington DC, Pennsylvania (Box 55)
  - New York (Box 55)
  - Oklahoma, Tennessee, Texas (Box 55)
  - Oklahoma, Tennessee, Texas (Box 55)
  - Dance Touring Program Directory, Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 56)
  - Lists Of Applicants Whereabouts (Galley's Etc.) (Box 56)
  - Companies Interested In CRTP, 1974-1975 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program Directory, Touring Sch., 1973-1974 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines, 1974-1975 (Box 56)
  - NEA, Dance Touring Program Estimates and Costs (actual), Printing, Shipment (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program Directory Corrections (Box 56)
  - Directory Of Dance Companies Contents, 1975 (Box 56)
  - NEA, CRTP, Touring Schedule, 1973-1974 (Box 56)
  - Administrator's List Dance Touring Program, 1975 (Box 56)
  - Printing Estimates and Bills, 1971-1972 (Box 56)
  - Correspondence, Letter, Jan. 30, 1974 (Box 56)
  - DTP Requests, FY, 1975 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program, Directory of Dance Companies, 1974-1975 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program Directory, Bills, D.P.O.V., 1973-1975 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program, 1977 (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program, 1967-1969 (Box 56)
  - Residency Touring Section 1, 1969-1970 (Box 56)
  - Residency Touring Section II, 1969-1970 (Box 56)
  - Residency Touring Section II, 1969-1970 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program, 1971-1972 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program, 1977 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring Program Directory, Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
  - Piper Pickrell (Box 56)
  - Laura Toffell Knox (Box 56)
  - Dena Davida (Box 56)
  - Lotte Goslar's Pantomime Circus (Box 56)
  - Fusion/Linda Diamond (Box 56)
  - Edith Stephan Dance Co. (Box 56)
  - Raymond Johnson Dance Company (Box 56)
  - The Moving Co. (Box 56)
  - Dibba Hamilton (Box 56)
  - Helaine B. Apostol (Box 56)
  - Walter Nicks Dance Theatre, Wksp. (Box 56)
  - Bruce King Dance Concert (Box 56)
  - Americana Dance Theatre (Box 56)
  - Darlene Handler (Box 56)
  - Consultants (Box 56)
  - Consultants (Box 56)
  - DMS/Co. Applicant, Master File, 1976-1977 (Box 57)
  - FY DTP Directory Master File, LG, 1976 (Box 57)
  - DTP Directory, FY, NEA Grant File, 1976 (Box 57)
  - FY, DTP Directory Of Dance Cos., Billing File (estimates and bills), 1976 (Box 57)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program, 1970-1974 (Box 57)
  - CRTP Problems and Solutions (Box 57)
  - Dance Co's Information, NEACRTP, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Company Publicity Material (Box 57)
  - NEA/CRTP Booking Sheets Co. Information, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Midwest Circuit (Box 57)
  - Great Lakes Circuit (Box 57)
  - South Circuit (Box 57)
  - West Coast Circuit (Box 57)
  - Southwest Circuit, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - New England Circuit, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Mid Atlantic Circuit, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Company Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - State Arts Councils Correspondence, 1970 (Box 57)
  - NEA/CRTP Company Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 1970 (Box 57)
  - Company Correspondence (Box 57)
  - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 57)
  - Press (Box 57)
  - Press (Box 57)
  - Rolodex Of States (Box 58)
  - Rolodex Of States (Box 58)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program, 1969-1971 (Box 59)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program, 1969-1971 (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Clippings, Photography Negatives, 1965-1966 (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Printed Materials (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor, 1965-1966 (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor, 1966-1967 (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor, 1964-1965 (Box 59)
  - Contracts, 1966-1967 (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor Tours, 1963-1964 (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor Contracts (Box 59)
  - Paul Taylor Contracts (Box 59)
  - AIS R50-51-47N, Cash Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - AIS/DC Grant R-50-51-7N, Final Report, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - AIS R50-51-47N, Grant Letter (Box 59)
  - NEA Contract, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - AIS Ledger Sheets and Calender, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - AIS/DC Grant R50-51-4 7N, Expenses DMS and ADMS, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - AIS Grant Applications and Budget Specifications, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - Senehan, Inc., AIS/DC National Coordination, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - DMS Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - DMS Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - AIS Contract File, Dance Movement Specialists, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - AIS Contract File, Asst. Dance Movement Specialists, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - Assistant Dance Movement Specialist, Resumes and Social Security Number, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Expenses, Card 90-62 from CC (Box 60)
  - Workshop Housing And Billing Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop/Mtg. Preliminary Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop, Grant R-50-51-4 7N Expenses, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Planning, Reimbursements, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - AIS/DC West Coast Coordinator Sheets, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - AIS/DC NEA State Grant Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - SAA AIS Grant Applications, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Alabama, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Arizona, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Alaska, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - California, Volume II, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Connecticut, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Delaware, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Florida, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Hawaii, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Hawaii, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
  - Michigan, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Minnesota, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - New Jersey, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Nevada, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - North Carolina, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - North Dakota, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Ohio, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Oklahoma, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Oregon, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Pennsylvania, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Puerto Rico, 1972-1974 (Box 61)
  - Tennessee, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Washington State, 1973-1974 (Box 61)
  - Requests for Applications, 1980-1981 (Box 61)
  - Applicant Review 1979-1980 Mini-Panel Meeting, Nov. 17, 1978 (Box 61)
  - Mistaken Application (RDT) 1979-1980 Supplemental Directory (Box 61)
  - Application Announcement (Box 61)
  - Jacque Lynn Bell (Box 61)
  - Joan Berstein (Box 61)
  - Joan G. Burns (Box 61)
  - Tedrian Chizik (Box 61)
  - Elinor Coleman (Box 61)
  - Penny Dudleston (Box 61)
  - Jan Erkert (Box 61)
  - Patricia Hruby (Box 61)
  - Judith Janus (Box 61)
  - Cathy Kaemmerlen (Box 61)
  - Susan B. Kaller (Box 61)
  - Aisha Khabeera (Box 61)
  - Karen Kristin (Box 61)
  - Maria Jimena Lasansky (Box 61)
  - Gretchen MacLane (Box 61)
  - Diana Martin (Box 61)
  - Jose Martin (Box 61)
  - Teodoro Morca (Box 61)
  - Judith Nelson (Box 61)
  - Paula Nelson (Box 61)
  - Ronald Payton (Box 61)
  - Suzanne Renner (Box 61)
  - Andrea Sherman (Box 61)
  - Robert Wilson (Box 61)
  - Dennis A. Wright (Box 61)
  - Kay Wylie (Box 61)
  - Joyce Zyznar (Box 61)
  - Tandy Beal and Company (Box 61)
  - Tandy Beal and Company (Box 61)
  - Tennessee, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Texas, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Utah, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Vermont, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Washington, 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Calendars (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Payment Schedule Budget Projections, 1978-1979 (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Letters to Accompany Checks, 1978-1979 (Box 62)
  - NEA: AIS/DC Phase Two r70-51-96 Correspondence with NEA, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - NEA: AIS/DC Phase Two r70-51-96 Cash Requests, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Final Report Phase Two Ford Foundation Grant #77-466 (Box 62)
  - AIS Follow-Up Ford Foundation Approach (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Ford Foundation Grant Letter 770-0466, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Notes Phase Two (Box 62)
  - AIS/DC Phase Two Announcement of Grants, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Panel, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Announcement of Grants form Ford/NEA, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Availability of Dance Movement Spec., 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Notes Phase Two Review of Applications (Box 62)
  - AIS Dance Component Phase Two Forms (Box 62)
  - Draft of Calendars Phase Two (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Worksheets for Final Report and Forms for Phase Two (Box 62)
  - Final Report NEA Grant R70-51-96 Phase Two AIS/Dance Component (Box 62)